在看过了那么多事情之后
After everything we've seen,
很少能有再让我们惊慌的了
there isn't much that rattles either of us anymore.
然而这个
But this one…
依旧阴魂不散
This one still haunts me.
（纽约 阿米蒂维尔）
在我们介入前的两个月
Two months prior to our involvement,
卢兹一家在半夜逃离了家门
the Lutz family had fled their home in the middle of the night,
声称房子闹鬼
claiming that the house was haunted.
教堂向我们寻求帮助
The Church had reached out to us for help.
他们想知道
They wanted to see
我们能否确认
if we could confirm the
卢兹一家报告的事是否属实
activity that had been reported by the Lutzes.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
好了 准备好了吗
Okay. We ready?
那么开始吧
Then let's get started.
我希望你们安静地坐下 闭上眼睛
I'd like you to sit quietly and close your eyes.
想象自己在闪着白光的光晕里面
Envision yourself in a halo of glowing white light.
它会保护你们
It will protect you.
卢兹家搬进这里之前的一年
The year before the Lutzes moved in,
一名叫罗尼·笛福的年轻男人
a young man named Ronny DeFeo
在这座房子里残忍地杀害了他的整个家庭
had brutally murdered his entire family in this house.
我们希望了解
We'd hoped to discover if
这次杀戮是否纯粹是因为愤怒
the killings had been motivated purely by anger
还是说 像罗尼·笛福 在法庭作证时所说的
or if, as Ronny DeFeo testified in court,
他被一些邪恶的东西操控了
he had been under the influence of something demonic.
留在这儿 留下
Stay here. Stay.
杀了她 杀了她
Kill her. Kill her.
开枪
Shoot them.
杀了他们
Shoot them!
射死她
Shoot her!
你做了什么
What did you do?
开枪 杀了她
Shoot her. Kill her.
杀了她
Shoot her!
把他们都杀死
Shoot them all.
开枪
Shoot!
杀
Kill!
杀了她 开枪
Kill her. Shoot her.
亲爱的 你还好吗 你看到了什么
Honey, you okay? What are you seeing?
罗琳
Lorraine.
罗琳 发生了什么
Lorraine, what is happening?
我必须知道
I have to see.
时间到了 时间到了 该回来了
We're through. We're through. It's time to come back.
发生了什么
What is happening?
它想给我看些东西
It wants to show me.
罗琳
Lorraine!
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God! Oh!
亲爱的
Honey.
没事了
It's okay.
埃德
Ed.
这是我能忍受的最接近地狱地方
This is as close to hell as I ever wanna get.
（沃伦夫妇在阿米蒂维尔的调查 引起了媒体的关注 同时把此事推向了大众的视线中）
（与此同时 许多人会和阿斯蒂维尔相比较的事件 发生在英格兰的恩菲尔德）
（距离此地千万里远处 这可能是涉及到沃伦夫妇处理的恶魔事件中最严峻的一次）
（基于真实故事改编）
《招魂2》
- 讨厌的小孩 - 是啊
- Damn kids! - Really.
是啊
Yeah.
哦 上帝
Oh, my gosh.
我和基思
Keith and I are going to
打算和他朋友迈克尔偷偷溜出去
sneak out tonight with his friend, Michael,
顺便说句 他很想见你
who wants to meet you, by the way.
不行 如果被我妈妈发现就死定了
No way. If my mum ever found out, I'd be dead.
那就别被发现啊 ⁮娘娘腔
So don't get caught, you priss.
嘿 拿着这个
Here, hold this.
我把我们做的通灵板还给你
Gotta give you back the spirit board that we made.
我想我会让基思法式热吻我
I think I'll let Keith French kiss me.
什么 认真的吗
What? No way!
你们两个在干什么
What you two doing?
珍妮特 把烟拿来
Janet, give that to me.
你们两个 进屋去
And get inside, both of you.
快点
Go.
玛 玛 玛格丽特
M-M-M-M-Margaret.
玛格丽特 约翰尼
Margaret! Johnny!
珍妮特 比利
Janet! Billy!
你好呀 今天过得怎么样
Hello. How was your day?
不怎么样
Not good.
为什么 怎么了
Why? What happened?
一言难尽 我之后再告诉你
It's a long story. I'll tell you later.
好吧
All right, then.
最 最 最近怎么样
W-w-what's up?
比 比 比利
B-B-B-B-Billy?
闭嘴 彼得
Shut up, Peter.
蕾丝边
Lesbo!
什么 你在说你妈吗
What, are you talking about your mum?
哦
Oh.
谢谢你 卡米拉
Thank you, Camilla.
没事
No problem!
他就是个傻逼 别理他
He's just a wanker. Ignore him.
好吧
Okay.
（恩菲尔德小学）
（格林街）
- 妈妈会杀了我的 - 你干了什么
- Mum's gonna kill me. - What did you do now?
不是我 是卡米拉
It wasn't me, it was Camilla.
你和卡米拉干什么了
What did you do with Camilla?
- 一言难尽 - 孩子们 看路
- It's a long story. - Boys! Watch the road!
- 珍妮特 - 上吧 比利
- Janet! - Up you go, Billy.
噢
Ow!
来吧
Come on.
（霍奇森家 英格兰 恩菲尔德 1977）
我是说 我这个月付不了房租
I'm saying I won't be able to pay my rent this month.
不 我和他们说了 他们让我和你说
No. I talked to them, and they put me through to you.
保持冷静
Please keep calm…
我很冷静
I am being calm.
我不理解为什么你不能帮帮我
Well, I don't understand why you can't help me.
不
No.
不 他赡养费三个月来一分钱都没付
No. He hasn't paid a penny of child maintenance for three months.
- 我们回来了 - 我看到了 真他妈棒啊
- We're home! - I see. That's bloody brilliant.
- 嗨 妈妈 - 也祝你下午好
- Hi, Mum! - You have a good afternoon as well.
珍妮特
Janet.
还嫌事情不够多么
Are things not bad enough around here,
我接到你校长的电话了
that I've got to get a call from your headmistress
她说她抓到你抽烟
who says that you was caught smoking?
我没有 我没有抽烟
I wasn't! I wasn't smoking. I promise.
- 你收到饼干了么 - 你听见我说话了么
- Did you get the biscuits? - Did you just not hear me?
我和莫尔女士在电话里谈过了
I talked to Mrs. More on the telephone.
你怎么能当着面这样对我撒谎
How can you stand there and lie to me like that?
我没有撒谎
I'm not lying!
她就是在撒谎 整个学校都知道了
Yes, she is! It's all over the school.
她和卡米拉在一起抽烟
She was smoking with Camilla.
闭嘴 约翰尼 你就是个骗子
Shut up! You are such a liar, Johnny!
妈妈 你说过你会给我带
Mum! You said we would get me some…
没 比利 我他妈没买饼干
No, Billy. I didn't get any bloody biscuits
因为我们他妈的没钱
because we don't have any bloody money!
妈妈要上来了
Mum's coming.
别乱折腾了 快去刷牙
You better quit messing with that and brush your teeth!
好啦
All right.
听起来像是整个城市都烧起来了
Sounds like the whole city's burning down in here.
看看我找到了什么
Look what I found!
饼干
Biscuits!
可你说过我们没钱
But you said we don't have any money.
反正我准备要戒烟的 省下了
Well, I've been meaning to quit smoking anyway.
- 玛格丽特 - 什么
- Margaret? - Yes?
准备好明天的校服了吗
Have you got your school uniform for tomorrow?
好了 妈妈 我正在弄
Yes, Mum. I'm getting it.
约翰尼 你刷牙了么
Johnny, did you brush your teeth?
我刷过了
I did it already.
快来 比利 该睡觉了
Come on, Billy. Time for bed.
马上来 妈妈
Coming, Mum.
放下 约翰尼 该睡觉了
Put that down, Johnny. Come on. Time for bed.
哇哦 这是哪儿来的
Oh, where'd that come from?
卡米拉和我在学校做的
Camilla and I made it at school.
看起来不行啊
Ugh. That doesn't look right.
真的有用 我发誓
It really works, I swear.
我们已经问了各种各样的东西了
We already asked it all sorts of stuff.
来 我弄给你看
Come on, I'll show you.
好吧
All right.
我应该问什么
What should I ask?
我不知道 什么都行
I don't know. Whatever you want.
好吧
Okay.
我妹妹和我想知道
My sister and I want to know…
有没有灵魂愿意和我们交流
Are there any spirits here that want to communicate with us?
爸爸还会回来吗
Is Dad ever coming home?
有鬼魂愿意回答我的问题吗
Are there any spirits here who can answer my question?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
只是个愚蠢的游戏
It's just a stupid game.
不是真的
It isn't real.
你为什么拍门
Why're you pounding on the door?
我没有
I'm not.
你真傻
You're barmy.
你知道 她正在测试我的极限
You know, she's pushing the boundary, isn't it?
她说她没有抽烟
She says she wasn't smoking.
我不是说我对此感到烦恼 佩格
I don't think you should agonize over it, Peg.
天知道 你们在学校也得做苦差事 是吧
God knows I had my share of fags at school, didn't you?
是啊 可多了
Oh, lots.
她做的那些事并没有困扰我
But it's not what she did that bothers me.
是她不听我话了 佩吉
It's that, she don't listen to what I say anymore, Pegs.
就这个阶段嘛 是不是
Just a phase, isn't it?
对 我是能惩罚她 可之后我会愧疚
I mean, I can punish her, but then I feel guilty
因为我也不好说就是她错了
because I know it's not really her fault.
她爱她爸爸
She loves her dad and she
他离开的时候 她真的很难过 可怜的小姑娘
took it very hard when he left. Poor thing.
但这事也不能就这样算了 对吧
But I can't just let it go either, can I?
我不太想这么问 不过 你告诉理查德了吗
I'm loath to ask, but have you told Richard about it?
我会的 如果我能见到他
I would, if I ever saw him.
该死
Sod.
现在就像我要同时做两份工作
Now, it's like I'm having to do both jobs.
其中一半 我得像以前般做好妈妈 我糟透了 佩吉
I'm half the mum I was before. I'm just rubbish, Peggy.
才不是 佩吉 别对自己太苛刻
You are not, Peggy. You're too hard on yourself.
- 哦 - 哦
- Ooh! - Oh!
- 见鬼的房子 - 哦
- This sodding house! - Oh!
我们又见面了 还有现实生活中的恶灵猎人
We are back with real life ghost hunters, Ed and Lorraine Warren,
埃德和罗琳·沃伦夫妇将来谈谈他们在阿米蒂维尔之屋的经历
talking about their experiences at the Amityville house.
现在 我们要问问另一位客人
And now we're gonna talk to my next guest,
斯蒂夫·卡普兰博士
Dr. Steven Kaplan, who says
他说沃伦夫妇对阿米蒂维尔闹鬼事件的调查
that the investigations the Warrens conducted
是胡说八道
into the Amityville haunting is a load of hogwash.
为什么这么说呢
Why is that?
好吧 可以说
Well, it's been well
阿米蒂维尔事件就是个明目张胆的骗局
established that Amityville was a blatant hoax.
- 但这没有 - 这点从未被证实
- But that hasn't stopped… - That's never been proven.
当然有过
Yes, it has.
卢兹夫妇伪造了一切
The Lutz family made everything
那样他们就能从宣传中获利了
up so they could profit off of all the publicity.
那不是真的
That's just not true.
你看 我们一直以来都是这样的
Look, we see this all the time.
从旁观者的角度挑一段故事 这很容易
It's very easy to sit on the outside and pick apart their story.
但你自己去那里真实地体验
But it's something very different
这就是另一回事了
to have been there and experienced it for yourself.
我可不需要真的登上月球
I don't need to go to the moon
才知道它不是「生干酪」做成的
to know that it's not made out of green cheese.
听着 埃德·沃伦去过的屋子
Listen, Ed Warren's never
就没有他认为不闹鬼的
seen a house that he didn't think was haunted.
他妻子放完烟雾弹 吸引注意力之后
And by the time his wife is done blowing smoke and ringing bells
他们让其他所有人都相信闹鬼了
they've got everybody else believing in ghosts, too.
你到底是哪门子的博士
What exactly are you a doctor of, anyway?
天啊沃伦 优雅一点行吗
Come on, Warren. Try and show a little class, will you?
我才不想给那些坐在这里
I'm not gonna show class to somebody
讲我和我妻子坏话的人尊重
who's sitting here telling lies about my wife and me.
注意点 你叫谁骗子呢
Be careful who you call a liar.
我就说了 怎么着
What are you gonna do about it?
我们来录这些节目是为了告知人们
We go on these shows to inform people.
但是每次我开口 都有那些
But every time I open my mouth, another one of these little…
- 埃德 - 狗
- Ed. - Ass…
学者们
Academics…
冒出来
Pops up.
试图诋毁我们所做的一切
Tries to undo everything we've done.
- 你能消停会儿吗 - 我知道 我知道
- Could you please take a breath? - I know. I know. I know.
我知道 我会数到十 数到十
I'm counting to 10. I'm counting to 10!
好了比利
All right, Billy.
准备好演讲了吗
You ready to do a speech?
没事 我们再来一次
It's all right. We'll just try again.
准备好了么
You ready?
（驼背的男人）
好样的
Good boy!
做得非常好 给你个饼干
You're getting so good. Now you may have a biscuit.
饼干
Biscuit!
好了 该睡觉了
All right. Come on. Off to bed with you.
- 晚安 妈妈 - 晚安
- Night, Mom. - Good night, darling.
别吃这么多了
Now, don't eat too many of those
省的半夜口渴醒来 好吗
or you'll wake up thirsty in the middle of the night. All right?
我不会的
I won't.
你保证
You promise?
- 晚安 孩子们 - 晚安 妈妈
- Night, boys. - Night, Mom.
不
No.
救救我
Help.
不要
Stop it.
不
No.
珍妮特
Janet?
- 拜托 - 珍妮特
- Please. - Janet?
珍妮特 快醒醒 你在做噩梦
Janet, wake up! You're dreaming.
这是我的家
This is my house.
不 这不是
No. No, it's not.
滚出去
Go away.
你是谁 你在这里做什么
Who are you? What are you doing here?
我在和比利玩
Playing a game with Billy.
别碰比利
Leave Billy alone.
珍妮特 你在和谁说话
Janet, who are you talking to?
你快走开
You have to go away.
你才是那个擅闯别人家的人
You're the one trespassing.
珍妮特 快醒醒
Janet, wake up.
你再不停下来 我要告诉我妈妈了
I'll tell my mum if you don't stop.
我会拧断她的脖子
I'll break her neck.
不 求你了
No, please.
和比利一起死去
Dying with Billy.
不
No.
珍妮特
Janet.
珍妮特 没事了
Janet, it's all right.
没事了没事了
It's all right, come on.
好好睡吧
Go back to sleep.
不许伤害比利
Stay away from Billy!
离我们远点 你听到了么
Leave us alone. You hear me?
珍妮特 你在做什么 那里没人
Janet, what are you doing? There's no one here.
这是我的家
This is my house.
妈妈 妈妈
Mum! Mum!
比利 怎么了
Billy? What's wrong?
有人在我的帐篷里
There's someone in my tent!
什么
What?
有人在我的帐篷里
There's someone in my tent!
妈妈
Mummy.
你看 什么都没有
See? Nothing.
你只是做噩梦了 就这样而已
You just had a bad dream. That's all.
回房间睡吧
Go to your room.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
珍妮特
Janet!
我心脏病都要被你吓出来了 你怎么下楼了 你在做什么呢
You nearly gave me a heart attack. What're you doing down here?
我想 我又梦游了
I think I've been sleepwalking again.
又梦游了 什么意思
What do you mean "Again"?
你还好吗
You all right?
你在发烧
You're burning up. Come on.
我们回房间吧 好吗
Come on, let's get you back upstairs, eh?
我想你明天就不用去学校了
Think you better stay home from school tomorrow.
我们先回去睡觉吧 好吗
Come on. Let's get you back into bed, eh?
你知道我想做一个讨厌的艺术家
You know I want to be a
并且成为一名可靠的画家
hair artiste and become a credible painter.
别给我那些野蛮的宣传或者是异想天开的讨厌的…
Don't give me any of your brute hype and airy-fairy hair…
倒退30年
…back 30 years.
现在我回到10岁时
Now, I've gone back to the age of 10.
所有东西都是用软焦点拍的
Everything is shot in soft focus.
一些虚构的借口
Some bogus excuses.
你准备什么时候离开那豪华的学校
When're you gonna leave that posh school, eh?
然后找一份适合男人的工作在…
And get yourself a proper man's job down…
是的 一首圣诞颂歌
Yes, a Christmas carol.
- 哪一个 - 所有的
- Which one? - All of them.
几分钟内
And within minutes…
主席先生 总统先生 女士们 先生们
Mr. Chairman, Mr. President, ladies and gentlemen.
今晚我站在你们面前
I stand before you tonight,
身着红星雪纺晚礼服
in my Red Star chiffon evening gown.
霍奇森家
Hodgson residence.
妈妈
Oh. Hi, Mum.
嗯 有一点
Yeah, a little.
我刚吃过 所以不怎么饿
I just ate, so I'm not really that hungry.
嗯 我在听
Yeah. I'm here.
您什么时候回来啊
Do you know when you'll be home?
好吧
All right.
再见 妈妈
Bye, Mum.
是的 我就说铁娘子
Yes, I am an iron lady.
西方世界的铁娘子
The Iron Lady of the Western world.
不 不 你很坏 你知道 你
No, no. You are a bad one, you know, you.
亲爱的母亲 抱歉我迟到了
Mother dearest, I'm sorry I am late.
但我必须停下给你买有益健康的黑面包
But I had to stop off to get you a health-giving brown loaf.
我不想听到这种理由
I do not wish to hear about that sort of thing.
我想要你过来
I want you to come over here,
如果你不介意 让你老妈
if you don't mind me, and let your old mum
帮你刮了肚脐上的绒毛
scrape the fluff out of your belly button.
在大游行上漂亮又干净 而且在星期天很适合
Nice and clean for the big parade and very good on Sunday.
我应该在那 你知道的 看着你
I shall be there, you know, watching you.
这是我的家
My house!
你起的好早
You're up early.
我睡不着
Hey. Yeah, I couldn't sleep.
你有灵感了
You get inspired?
我不觉得
I don't know if I'd call it that.
我做了一个疯狂的梦
I had this crazy dream.
当我醒来的时候
Saw this thing.
我看到了这个
When I woke up…
一直困扰着我
Couldn't get it out of my head.
我想画下来也许会有帮助
So, thought maybe this might help.
嘿 我知道我不是毕加索 但我画的没那么差吧
Hey, I know I'm no Picasso, but I didn't think it was that bad.
我们该收山了
We need to stop.
可以做讲座 但不要接新案子了
We could still do the lectures, but no new cases.
起码歇一阵子
At least not for a little while.
好吧
All right. Uh…
能告诉我为什么吗
Could I ask why?
如果是因为电视节目或是公关 那我们就不去
Because if it's the TV shows and publicity then we won't do that.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
早
Morning.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
当然了
You know I do.
相信我就好了
Then please trust me now.
好
Okay.
你那是在做什么呢
Oh. What are you doing that for?
以防万一我又梦游
In case I go sleep walking again.
妈妈
Mum?
约翰尼
Johnny?
珍妮特 怎么了 这是什么
Janet! What's wrong? What is it?
我们房间里有人
There's someone in the room!
没有人 你在说些什么
There's no one! What you talking about?
- 妈妈 我们房间里有人啊 - 什么
- There's someone in our room! - What!
我们的床不停得晃
Our beds are shaking up and down!
珍妮特 我发誓 如果你在撒谎
Janet, I swear to God if you're making it up…
我没有 你看 他咬我了
I got bit. I'm not lying! He bit me! Look!
天哪
Oh, my God.
你们刚刚是不是在玩这个
Have you two been playing with this?
轮流去吓唬对方
Taking turns scaring the wits out of each other?
怪不得你们都睡不着
No wonder I can't get a good night's sleep!
- 妈妈 不是的 - 别说了 我不想听你们继续撒谎
- But, Mum… - No! I don't wanna hear another word.
你们俩马上上床睡觉
Now get back to bed, the lot of you!
救命
Help us!
- 救命啊 - 救命
- Please help! - Help!
佩吉 维克 开门
Peggy! Vic, open the door!
开门
Open the door!
我亲眼所见
I've seen it with my own eyes.
那该死的东西穿过了整个房间
The bloody thing went clear across the room.
但是
But…
- 然后 - 什么
- Well, then… - What? Well?
很冷 我仔细地检查了房子
It's cold. Well, I've been through the house.
什么人都没有
Top to bottom. There's no one there.
玛格丽特和珍妮特的房间呢
What about Margaret and Janet's room? Did you…
嗯 我去看了
No, no. I looked there, every room.
地下室我都去看过了 我没看到什么人
Even went down the basement. There's no one there.
他在做什么
What's he doing?
我们教他 当他想上厕所时就摇这个铃
We've taught him to ring the bell when he wants to go.
让它出去吧 比利
Do you wanna let him out, Billy?
快 快看 警察去我们家了
Look! The police are at our house!
他们怎么来了
Now, what they doing here?
- 我报的警 - 什么
- Oh, I called them. - What?
一定是有人在恶作剧
Well, I mean, it's got
不是吗
to be somebody playing a joke on you, right?
没准是的
It's got to be. Yeah.
所以不是只有您看到那个人 对吗 女士
So, ma'am. You didn't actually see the man yourself?
恩
No.
看起来那个人是你们编造出来的
But I don't think she's making it up. Not anymore.
听着 我觉得这一切肯定能有个解释
Well, look. There has to be some sort of explanation.
先生 这就是我们在这里的原因 好吗
Sir, that's why we're here, okay?
从厨房给我拿一张椅子
Bring me a chair from the kitchen.
音来自墙体里面
It's coming from inside the wall.
那是什么呢 也许是老鼠
Then what? Mice, maybe?
该死的老鼠
Big bloody mouse.
我们对此无能为力
Well, there's nothing we can do about that.
我们会提交一个报告
We can file an incident
如果你需要的话 我们随时待命
report and we'll stand by it if anyone asks.
就这么多了
But that's about all.
报告 哦 真是太棒了
A report? Oh. That's brilliant.
我所遇到的问题都特么填一个表格就解决了吗
Every problem I have, there's another bloody form to fill out!
天啊 难以置信
Oh, for God's sake.
听着
Listen.
这超出了我们的能力范围
I think this is a bit beyond us.
我认识一个神父
The priest at our church is a family friend.
我会让他来帮助你们的
I'll ask him to call on you.
还有一些诚实的人留在这个世界
There are still some honest people left in the world.
而且她说 发生的是
And she said, what happened was,
她在杂货店时
that she was at the grocery store.
她把钱包落在那了 在杂货店里
She left her wallet there, at the grocery store.
里面有钱 很多钱
It had money in it, a lot of money.
于是她想 好吧 就这样吧 已经没了
And she thought, "Well, that's that. It's gone."
她以为有人会把它捡走
She thought someone was just gonna pick it up.
就是这样
That's it, that's that.
但当想看看还能做什么
But just to see what she could do,
她回到了杂货店 果然
she went back to the grocery store and sure enough.
一个诚实的女士捡到了钱包
Some honest woman had picked up
并归还到了经理那
the wallet and returned it to the manager there.
她找回了所有东西 包括她的钱
She got everything back. She got her money.
她拿回了手袋里的所有东西
She got everything that was in the purse.
朱迪
Judy?
亲爱的
Honey…
怎么了
What's wrong?
妈妈
Mom.
那是谁
Who's that?
快回去
Go back.
你是谁
Who are you?
告诉我 你是谁
Tell me who you are!
- 妈妈 妈妈 快醒醒 - 不
- Mom! Mom. Mom! Wake up! - No!
你想要什么
What do you want?
对不起 洛林
I'm sorry, Lorraine.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
霍奇森夫人
Mrs. Hodgson.
恩
Yes?
我叫 肯特·艾伦
My name's Kent Allen.
我在做一档电视新闻节目 叫广角
We're with the television news program Wide Angle.
我想和您谈谈
I was hoping to have a word with
关于上周您家里发生的事儿
you about the disturbance at your home last week.
你怎么知道的
How'd you find out about that?
警员写了一个报告
The police constables filed an incident report. It's…
那个报告让我们很惊讶
Well, it's raised a few eyebrows.
我可不想自己的家事儿
I'd rather not have my business spread all over the telly,
出现在电视节目里 再见
if you don't mind. Good day!
那种情况还在发生吗
Is it still happening?
如果是的话 让大家知道你的故事
Because if it is getting your side of the story out
才是寻求帮助最好的选择
might be your best chance of finding help.
开机了吗 好吧
This thing on? Okay.
我们眼前这座看似平淡无奇的房子里
Behind the doors of this seemingly normal house
这一家人正生活在一场噩梦之中
in Ponders End, North London, is a family living in a nightmare.
我透过窗户往上看
I look up, and through the window,
能清楚看见小女孩 珍妮特
plain as day, I see the younger girl,
在天上飞 就好像她漂浮着
Janet, being thrown around in the air like she was floating.
我们赶紧跑回屋
So we run back inside and sure enough
那种小的乐高玩具砖块在整个房间里飞着
there's little toy LEGO bricks flying all around the room.
有一个还击中了我的右脸 太疼了 我都流血了
One of them hit me right in the face so hard it drew blood.
我看到那张椅子自己在地板上滑动
I saw the chair slide by itself,
就在我几步之遥的眼前移动
across the floor, a distance of several feet.
我检查了那张椅子是否连着电线什么的
I checked the chair for wires,
但没有 发生的一切无法解释
but could find nothing to explain it.
莫里斯·格罗斯是工程学方面的顾问
Maurice Grosse is an engineering consultant
他为了社会大众和物理研究
and has been investigating these
介入了此次调查
claims for the Society of Psychical Research.
我认为这不是一个问题
Well, I don't think there's any doubt about it at all.
在这起案件中 大量的文件
The sheer number of documented
都让人感到难以置信
incidents in this case is absolutely staggering.
但是 安尼塔·格雷戈里 一位通灵者
But, Anita Gregory, a parapsychologist
以及北伦敦理工学院的讲师
and lecturer at the Polytechnic of North London,
并不确信
is not convinced.
我们这的主角是所有孩子
Our principal characters here are all children.
孩子在恶作剧上是非常机灵的
And children can be very ingenious pranksters.
在这些可怕活动的中心人物
At the center of these
就是11岁的珍妮特·霍奇森
frightening activities is 11-year-old Janet Hodgson.
我最近采访了
I recently interviewed
珍妮特和她14岁的姐姐玛格利特
Janet and her 14-year-old sister, Margaret.
接下来发生的 会让你惊讶
What happened next will astonish you.
居住在闹鬼的房子里是一种什么体验
How does it feel living in a haunted house?
不好说
I don't know.
反正你不会喜欢的
You don't get used to it.
你瞧 发生这一切之前 我们只是平凡无奇的家庭
You see, we was just a normal family before all this.
事情变得越来越糟糕 自从格罗斯先生和它说话以后
It's been getting worse since Mr. Grosse started talking to it.
什么意思
How do you mean?
比如问问题时
Like, asking it questions.
说点头两次就代表是的 一次代表不是
Saying knock twice for "Yes" And one for "No."
类似这些
That sort of thing.
那如果我们现在试试跟它说话会怎么样
I wonder what would happen if we tried talking to it now?
有人在这么
Is anybody there?
有没有人想聊聊的
Is anybody there who wishes to communicate?
我再问一次 有人在这么
I say again, is anybody there?
没有么
Nothing.
它又不是自动点唱机 对么
Well, it isn't a jukebox, is it?
珍妮特 你还好么
Janet, are you all right?
珍妮特
Janet?
嗯哼
Mmm.
珍妮特
Janet.
珍妮特 你感觉还好么
Janet, are you feeling all right?
别叫我珍妮特
Stop calling me Janet!
珍妮特不是你的名字么
Isn't that your name?
珍妮特睡着了
Janet's asleep…
现在是我在说话
And I'm talking.
那么 阁下怎么称呼
Well, what should I call you?
你名字叫什么
What is your name?
你不属于这
You don't belong here.
我叫莫里斯·格罗斯
My name is Maurice Grosse.
你呢
Who are you?
这是我的房子
This is my home.
滚出去
Get out now!
不 这不是你的房子 现在告诉我你的名字
No. This is not your house. Now, what's your name?
咚 咚
Knock, knock.
很好
Very well.
谁在敲门
Who's there?
比尔 比尔
字幕
Bill. Bill.
I'd like you to leave, please.
比尔 比尔
Bill. Bill.
全名呢
Bill who?
我叫比尔·威金斯 我72岁
My name is Bill Wilkins and I'm 72 years old.
你们觉得是谁发出来的这种声音
Where do you come from?
我从坟墓里来
I come from the grave.
你怎么死的
How did you die?
我失明了还流了很多血
I went blind and had a hemorrhage.
我阖了眼睑 死于角落里的椅子上
And I fell asleep and I died in the chair in the corner.
你为什么来这里
Why have you come here?
我喜欢听到惊恐的尖叫
I like to hear them scream.
你为什么不能远离我们
Why don't you just leave us alone?
闭嘴 你这头老母牛
Shut up, you old cow!
珍妮特 亲爱的
Janet, darling.
亲爱的你还好么
Darling, are you all right?
对不起
I'm sorry.
珍妮特
Janet.
佩吉 我该怎么办
Peggy, what am I gonna do?
噢
Oh…
今晚别想那么多了
You don't need to think about it tonight.
而且你和孩子们想待多久都可以
And you and the kids can stay here as long as you like.
妈妈
Mum.
比尔 你现在不应该准备睡觉了么
Billy, aren't you supposed to be getting ready for bed?
我 我想你可能想来点饼干
I thought you might like some biscuits.
噢
Oh…
噢 谢谢你
Oh, thank you!
巴伦
Baron?
妈妈 妈妈
Mum! Mum!
- 发生什么了 怎么了 - 是驼背男人
- What happened? What is it? - The Crooked Man!
什么驼背 亲爱的你在说什么
What? Crooked what? What are you talking about, darling?
- 驼背的男人 - 冷静
- The Crooked Man! - Calm down!
告诉我发生什么了
Just tell me what happened.
- 发生什么了 - 怎么了
- What? - What is it?
我不知道 我觉得他看到什么了
I don't know. I think he's been walking around…
珍妮特
Janet!
Janet?
我的老天
Oh, my God! No!
快去叫救护车
Someone get an ambulance!
这是我的房子
This is my home.
滚出去
Get out now.
不 这不是你的房子 现在 告诉我你的名字
No. This is not your house. Now, what's your name?
咚 咚
Knock, knock.
真好笑 谁在敲门
Very well. Who's there?
比尔 比尔
Bill. Bill.
全名呢
Bill who?
我叫比尔·威金斯 我72岁
My name is Bill Wilkins and I'm 72 years old.
你们觉得是谁发出来的这种声音
What do you make of that voice?
有点不好说
He sounds confused.
是一个老人发出的
Is he senile?
录音带里的这个声音是从一个11岁的小女孩身体里发出的
The voice on this tape is coming from an 11 year old girl.
这个家庭有没有寻求教会的帮助
The family's reached out to the Church for help?
寻求了 但是
Yes.
说实话 我们很不愿意卷入这件事情
But truthfully, we've been reluctant to get involved.
这个案件已经成为了媒体关注的焦点
The case has turned into a media circus over there.
他们称之为英国版本的阿斯蒂维尔事件
They're calling it "England's Amityville."
太棒了
Great.
你怕这只是个恶作剧
You're afraid it's a hoax.
教会对人们的帮助取决于他们的名声
The Church's ability to help people depends on its reputation.
那你想我们做什么
So, what do you want us to do?
我们想让你们搭飞机去伦敦
We'd like you to fly to London
以作为我们为期三天非官方耳目的身份出现
for three days to act as our unofficial eyes and ears.
你们什么也不用做
Now, you don't have to do anything.
如果这是恶作剧 可以转身离开
If it is a hoax, you just turn around and leave.
但是如果不是恶作剧
But if it's not…
那么在伦敦有一家人急需我们的帮助
Then there is a family in London that desperately needs our help.
感谢你对我们的信任
Thank you for your faith in us.
- 有什么需求尽管告诉我 - 好的
- All right. Well, just let me know. - Okay.
我告诉他我们商量一下
I told him we'd talk about it.
没什么好商量的
There's nothing to talk about.
亲爱的 你都听到了
Honey, you heard him.
他们也不想我们过多参与
They don't want us to get involved.
观察一下然后做做报告
Just observe and report back.
我们经常拒绝案件没错
There have always been cases we've turned down.
但我们从来没有拒绝帮助一个家庭过
There has never been a family that we've refused to help.
我曾在阿斯蒂维尔家看到了
I had a vision in Amityville.
和七年前曾看见的一样
It was the same one I had seven years ago.
我遇见了你的死亡
I had a premonition of your death.
等等 这就是你封印自己能力八天的原因
Wait. That's why you locked yourself away for eight days?
你看到了我的死亡
You saw my death?
你也看到了
You've seen it, too.
你画中的恶魔是真实的
The demon in your painting is real.
我们都看到了同一个非人类鬼魂
We have both seen the same inhuman spirit.
这是一种警告 如果我们继续
It's a warning. If we keep doing this,
你会死的
you are going to die.
你的通灵能力是上帝赐予的礼物
Your visions are a gift from God.
如果上帝向你展示了我的死亡
And if God is showing you my death,
那么他做这些肯定是有理由的
then he's doing it for a reason.
也许是暗示你要阻止事情的发生
Maybe you're meant to prevent it from happening.
拜托
Come on.
面对抗争我们从不妥协
We don't run from fights.
如果我们去了
If we go…
如果我们这样做
If we do this…
你必须向我保证 我们只是先观察
You have to promise me that we're just there to observe.
如果任何事 以任何方式变得危险起来
If anything turns out dangerous in any way,
我们就告诉教会我们要离开
we're gonna tell the Church, and we're gonna get out.
答应我
Promise me.
答应我 爱德
Promise me, Ed.
我保证
I promise.
沃伦夫妇 我是莫里斯·格罗斯
Mr. And Mrs. Warren, I'm Maurice Grosse.
我对你们的到来表示衷心的感谢
Thank you so much for coming.
我猜你们会
I believe you're gonna be
就住在在霍奇森的房子里 对么
staying at the Hodgsons' house. Is that right?
几个人待在一起总是要好很多
Always better to be in the mix.
噢 没错 我同意
Oh, yeah. I agree.
就是这了
This is it.
谢谢你
Thank you very much.
我们到了
Here we are.
走吧
There we go.
爱德 我们打算拍摄一些令人惊讶的东西
Ed, we've managed to capture some amazing things.
我相信你看到了也会印象深刻的
I think you'll be very impressed when you see.
好的 我还想听听那些带子
Great. I'd like to listen to those tapes again, too.
那里面有些东西真的很有趣
You've got some really interesting stuff in there.
- 维克·诺丁汉 - 嗨 维克
- Vic Nottingham. - Hi, Vic.
你好 爱德·沃伦
How are you? Ed Warren.
你好 爱德
Hello, Ed.
你好吗 这是佩吉 佩吉·霍奇森
How are you? And this is Peggy, Peggy Hodgson.
- 很开心见到你 爱德·沃伦 - 幸会
- Nice to meet you. Ed Warren. - How do you do?
- 我妻子罗琳 - 幸会
- This is my wife, Lorraine. - How do you do?
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
那么 我走了 佩吉
Well, I'll be off then, Peg.
替我跟孩子问好好么
Will you tell the kids I said hello?
乐意之极
Yeah. Of course, I will. Nice to meet you.
- 幸会 - 我也是 霍奇
- Nice meeting you. - You too, hon.
- 那么开始吧 佩吉 - 行 快请进
- So, here we are, Peggy. - All right. Do come in.
只有我和珍妮特在
It's just me and Janet here now.
我其他的孩子和他们待在一起
My other kids are staying with them.
这以前是女孩们睡觉的地方 但是
This is where the girls used to sleep,
我们不再用这个房间了
but we don't use it anymore.
为什么不
Why not?
嗯 大部分的怪事都以这个房间为中心发生
Well, most of the activity centered in this room.
我们很担心有人会因此受伤
We were quite afraid that someone might get hurt,
所以就锁上了
which is why we keep it locked.
我听说珍妮特发生过漂浮现象了
I understand that Janet has levitated.
在这也发生过么
Did that happen in here as well?
- 是的 不止一次 - 是的
- Yeah, more than once. - Yeah.
我们同样拍了照片
We've got photographs of that as well.
我想听听霍奇森先生
I'd like to hear Mrs.
关于她事情的看法 如果你不介意的话
Hodgson's story from her, if you don't mind.
邻居们捐出来的十字架 我把它们挂起来
The neighbors donated them and I hung them up,
希望能阻止家具自己移动
hoping they'd keep things from moving around.
有用么
Has it worked?
没有 我们整晚都能听到东西移动
No. We can hear it all night.
你好 我是罗琳
Hi, there. I'm Lorraine.
介意我坐这里么
Mind if I have a seat?
你知道我为什么来这么
Do you know why I'm here?
你妈妈告诉了我发生的一切
Well, your mom has told me about what's been going on
于是 我来看看能否帮上忙
and I'm here to help, if I can.
关于发生的事情 你想谈谈么
Would you like to talk about it?
我在你这个年纪的时候
You know, when I was about your age,
有次我去医院看望我的母亲
um, I was visiting my mom at a hospital
然后 我看到了一个天使
and I saw an angel.
奇妙吧
Yeah.
它当时站在一个不用了的床边
It was standing next to a little boy's bed.
很轻柔的抚摸他的脸颊 然后它停下了
It was just gently touching his cheek and then it stopped.
直勾勾的望着我
And it looked right at me.
当然我妈妈和护士都不相信我
Of course, my mom and the nurses did not believe me,
但是我知道那是真的
but I knew it was real.
听着 我知道这种感觉
Look, I know how it is.
我知道失去朋友的滋味
I know what it's like to
因为你与众不同
lose your friends because you're different.
但是我同时也知道 一个人也可以改变一切
But I also know that one person can change everything.
你只需要做给他们看看
And you just have to open up to them.
你怎么知道你可以相信和你谈话的人
How did you know you could trust the people you opened up to?
我不知道
I didn't.
有时候也会因此受伤
Sometimes I got hurt.
还会花掉很多时间
And it took a long time,
但是我终于找到了相信我的人
but I finally found someone who believed me.
然后你做了什么
What did you do then?
我嫁给了他
I married him.
我真的太累了
I'm just so tired.
我不能在这儿睡
I can't sleep here.
我以前常去学校的医务室
I used to go to the medical
他们同意我睡在那儿
room at school and they let me sleep there
因为我太累了
because I was so worn out.
但是我现在连这样也不能做了
But now I can't even do that.
每个人都怕我
Everyone's afraid of me.
我一个朋友也没有
I got no friends.
没有地方可去
No place I can go to.
这让我觉得我不是个正常人
It makes me feel like I'm not normal.
你知道吗 不管是什么东西
You know, whatever is
他就想让你有这种感觉
doing this to you wants you to feel this way.
为什么啊
But why?
因为 这能让它变得更强大
Because that's what makes it stronger.
一切开始的时候
Around the time this all started,
珍妮特朝这儿走过来了 半夜的时候
Janet started waking up here in the middle of the night.
这个据点就是珍妮特说的 比尔 威尔金斯就死在这儿
This is the spot that Janet said Bill Wilkins died, right here.
你听谁说的
Where'd you get it from?
呃
Uh…
在我们搬进来的时候
My ex-husband bought all
我的前夫买下了所有的家具
the furniture with the house when we moved in.
如果你不介意我问一下的话
If you don't mind me asking…
你和前夫还有希望吗
Uh, is your ex-husband still in the picture?
不
Nope.
很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear that.
还有一点和解的余地吗
Any chance of reconciliation?
他和街角那个女人有一对双胞胎
He had twins with a woman from round the corner.
我理解为没有吧
So I'm gonna take that as a "No."
- 是的 还有很多事情要做 - 嗯
- Yeah, it's been a lot to deal with. - Hmm.
他走的那天带走了所有的音乐
He took all the music the day he left.
我知道很多人有时候会这么觉得
I know it must feel like that sometimes…
不 我的意思是 他真的拿走了所有唱片
No. I mean, literally. He took all the records.
我的孩子以前很喜欢听他的猫王的合集
My kids used to love listening to his Elvis collection.
- 他们经历的太多了 - 嗯
- They've been through so much. - Hmm.
现在这些事情才是首要
And now, all this is happening on top.
是的 这个时机并非巧合
Yeah. The timing isn't a coincidence.
这样负面的事件通常伴随着情绪的困扰
Negative entities often feed off emotional distress.
他们特别喜欢在你消沉的时候来把你击倒
They like to kick you when you're down.
当然 那看起来很不公平
That hardly seems fair.
是的 就是不公平
No, it really isn't.
你知道什么时候这声音会说话吗
Do you know when the voice is gonna speak?
偶尔
Sometimes.
当它说话的时候 你觉得是从你的内部发出来的吗
And when it does, does it feel like it's coming from inside you?
不
No.
是从我后面发出来的
More like it's coming from behind me.
就像我被利用了一样
Like I'm being used.
它是否曾经只对你一个人说过什么
Does it ever say things just to you?
或者只有你一个人可以听见
That only you can hear?
它说了什么
What does it say?
它说它想伤害你
It said it wants to hurt you.
它什么时候说的
When did it say that?
刚刚
Right now.
我们真的需要这么做吗
Do we really need that?
我希望能把它提供给教堂
We'd like to be able to prove to the Church
证明她不是自己发出的那些声音
that she's not making the voice herself.
所以让她嘴里喊着水 我们就能够证明
So, by holding the water in her mouth,
这不是她发出的腹语
we'll be able to show that it's not some form of ventriloquism.
她一定需要坐在那椅子那儿吗
Does she have to be in the chair?
只是
Just…
光是看着她那样坐在那儿 就让我不舒服
It makes me sick to see her sitting there like that.
你知道这很难 但是
We know it's hard, but the
有迹象表面这种幽灵附着在这个地方
spirit has shown an attachment to this spot.
如果她坐在那儿的话 埃德可以更容易的联系她
It'll be easier for Ed to contact it if she's sitting there.
你不会有事的
You'll be all right.
你准备好了吗
You ready for this?
大概吧
I guess so.
1997年12月21号
It's December the 21 st, 1977.
这是埃德和罗琳 沃伦
This is Ed and Lorraine Warren,
同佩吉和珍妮特·霍奇斯坐在一起
sitting with Peggy and Janet Hodgson.
同时在场的还有莫里斯·格罗斯
Also present is Maurice Grosse.
好的 我们开始吧
All right. Let's get started.
如果那儿有东西想要和我们沟通
If there's something here that would like to communicate with us,
我们都听着 说吧
we're all ears. Speak up.
你想要这个女孩儿和她的家人怎样
What do you want with this girl and her family?
它说它不想说话 如果你像这样看着我的话
It says it won't talk with you all looking at me like this.
奇怪 现在来这套
Strange! I wonder why not?
它之前怎么没有不好意思说话
It's not been shy about talking up until now.
要不我们都背过去吧
How about if we all turn our backs?
或许它会开口了吧
Think it'll speak if we do that?
或许吧
Maybe.
好吧
Well…
我们再试一次
Let's try this again.
你觉得呢 比尔
So what do you think, Bill?
我们给你私人空间了
We've given you your privacy.
现在出来和我们聊聊吧
Now come on out and talk to us.
我来了
Here I come.
我是在和困扰这个家庭的怨灵说话吗
Am I talking to the spirit that's oppressing this family?
你就是这样说我吗
Is that what I am?
你觉得我做的事是这样吗
Is that what I'm doing?
是的
Yes.
而且我要让你停止这种行为
And I have come to put a stop to it.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
埃德
Ed.
埃迪
Eddie.
爱德华
Edward.
叫埃德就好
Ed is fine.
你的父亲叫你爱德华
Your father called you Edward.
不是这样的
Not true.
我的父亲叫我埃德 同大家一样
My father called me Ed, just like everybody else.
算了吧比尔 你又不是精神病医生
Come on, Bill. You're not a psychiatrist
我也不是来这儿谈论我父亲的
and I'm not here to talk about my father.
说正事吧 你说如何
Let's get down to business, what do you say?
嗯
Hmm?
你为什么不放过这些人呢
Why don't you just leave these people alone?
因为这是我家
Because this is my house!
这不是你家
It's not your house.
就是的
Yes, it is.
我来这儿看我的家人
I come here to see my family,
但他们不在这儿
but they're not here now.
这是因为你死了
That's because you're dead.
如果你的家人不在这儿 他们早都离开了
If your family did live here, they're long gone now.
他们在哪儿
Where are they?
我不知道 如果我知道或许我能帮你
I don't know. If I did, maybe I could help you.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need your help.
那你为什么不放手呢
Then why don't you just move on?
我不信你这些鬼话
I don't believe in that.
为什么
Why not, hmm?
为什么 去天堂不好吗
What would be so wrong with going to heaven?
我不是
I am not
应该去天堂的人
a heaven man!
我有消息给你 比尔
Well, I got news for you, Bill.
看吧 我不关心你相信什么
You see, I don't care what you believe in.
你看到这个了吗
You see this?
救命 放 开 我
Help… it… let… go.
Help… It… Let… Go!
你能感到他的存在吗
Are you sensing a presence?
不 恰恰相反
No, just the opposite.
我没感觉到任何东西
I'm not sensing anything.
我们可能面对的是歇斯底里症
We could be looking at hysterical neurosis.
这就解释了多重性格
That would explain the multiple personalities
和幻觉
and hallucinations.
那感觉也不对
That doesn't feel right, either.
好吧
Well…
我也不知道为什么 我心里告诉我要相信他们
I can't explain it. My heart is telling me to believe them.
我听见了那声音 亲耳听到
I heard that voice with my own ears,
但是我能感到的只是他们的恐惧
but all I can sense is their own fear.
除了这 我什么都感觉不到
I can't seem to see beyond that.
我不觉得我离你那么远还能睡着
I don't think I can sleep this far away from you.
但是你没别的选择
Well, you're gonna.
等我们回到家的时候 我要给你留点可期待的事
It'll give you something to look forward to when we get home.
亲爱的 我希望你别这样
Oh, love. I wish you wouldn't do that.
这帮我入睡
It helps me sleep.
至少我知道我哪儿都不会去
At least I know I'm not going anywhere.
我不抽烟 妈妈
I didn't smoke, Mum.
什么
Eh?
那天和卡蜜拉在学校
That day with Camilla at school.
我是拿着烟
I was holding the cigarette,
但我没有打算抽 我发誓
but I wasn't going to take a puff. I swear.
我只是想在她面前看起来酷一点
I just wanted to look cool in front of her.
真蠢
It was stupid.
亲爱的
Oh, love.
很抱歉我没相信你
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, darling.
救命
Help!
嗯
Hmm.
珍妮特
Janet!
嗷
Ah!
珍妮特
Janet?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
珍妮特
Janet?
- 救命 - 珍妮特
- Help! - Janet?
珍妮特
Janet!
快救救我
Please help me!
妈妈
Mum!
快啊 妈妈
Please! Mum!
- 珍妮特 - 救命 让我出去
- Janet! - Help! Get me out!
有人在里面
There's somebody in here!
我打不开
I can't open it!
妈妈
Mum!
救救我
Help me!
珍妮特
Janet!
- 发生什么了 - 有个人在里面和珍妮特在一起
- What's going on? - There's someone in there with Janet!
我打不开
I can't get it open!
去拿钥匙 去拿钥匙 马上
Get the key. Go get the key now!
珍妮特 坚持住 我们来了
Janet! Hold on! We're coming!
我拿到钥匙了 我拿到钥匙了
I got the key! I got the key!
好 好
Okay. Okay.
快开啊
Come on.
珍妮特 我们来了
Janet, we're coming!
珍妮特
Janet.
把它从我身上拿开 求你了把它拿开
Get it off her! Please get it off her!
这是什么东西
What was that?
这里面有东西
There was someone in here!
我亲眼看见了
I saw him with me own eyes.
他让我女儿这样的
He did this to my girl.
这是珍妮特第一天晚上被咬的
This is the bite wound Janet received the first night.
已经消退了一点 但是还是能看出来
It's faded a bit here, but you can still make it out.
是啊 真的很不一样
Wow. That's pretty distinctive.
少了两个牙
Two missing teeth.
对啊 这牙比孩子们的牙都大
That's right. And it's too big for one of the children.
你觉得那是怨灵吗 比尔·威尔金斯吗
You think this was the spirit? This Bill Wilkins?
我调查了房主
I tracked down the home owner.
结果显示他的父亲曾在这儿住过
And it turns out, the owner's father lived there.
名字叫 威廉·威尔金斯
His name was William Wilkins and
他在那个椅子上脑溢血死亡
he died of a hemorrhage in the brain in that chair.
她说的都是真的
Everything she said is true.
但都是 公开的信息
All public information, by the way.
她可能从邻居那里听到了所有的事
She could have heard the whole story from a neighbor.
那她说的珍妮特在睡觉时
And what about the claims
在房子里游走又怎么解释
that Janet has been teleporting around the house in her sleep?
还有根有据 说她悬浮在她的床上
About as valid as their claims of her levitating off the bed.
发生的时候你们有人在那里吗
Were any of you there when it happened?
没有 但我有那时的照片
No. But I have pictures of that too.
是的 给你
Yeah. There you go.
我在女孩的房间架设了照相机
I set my camera up in the girls' room
然后我拿着遥控下楼
and then waited downstairs with the remote control.
每听到一点骚动就按下快门
And fired it off whenever I heard any commotion.
铁证如山
I have to admit.
她的膝盖折叠起来 但她的身体又是直的
The way her knees are bent, the upright position of her body.
看起来就像 要起跳
It looks like she's just jumping.
你在说什么 你昨晚就在她家
What are you saying? I mean, you were there last night.
你亲眼所见
You saw it with your own eyes.
嗯 佩吉看到了有人在攻击珍妮特
Well, Peggy was the one who saw someone attacking Janet.
但是她把自己锁在房间里
But she teleported herself into a room
远离外界 我的天呢
locked from the outside, for goodness' sake.
那她的声音呢
And what about her voice?
你要怎么解释
How do we explain that?
我觉得她第一次发出那种声音
I think the first time she was making that voice
是在摄像机前
it was in front of television cameras.
在你们移开视线前 她嘴里有水时
And she couldn't do it
无法发出那样的声音
with water in her mouth until you looked away.
所以 她可以吐出来
So she could have spit it out,
在你们转回来前抿一小口
taken another sip before you turned back.
去年我被威尔士家欺骗
Last year, I was conned by a
他们假装被恶魔控制
Welsh family pretending to be possessed by demons.
说实话 我不知道哪一种情况更可怕
Honestly, I don't know what was worse,
是有恶魔 还是人们
the demons or the people who
利用我们的善良去相信他们
prey on our willingness to believe in them.
恶魔更可怕
The demons are worse.
但是你不得不承认这很可疑
But you must admit, it is suspicious.
你真的觉得这一切都是她假装的吗
You sincerely believe that she's faking everything?
那佩吉呢
And what about Peggy?
或者她只是在利用整个事情做借口
She's just using the whole thing as an excuse
就可以从议会中得到更好的房子
to get better housing from the council.
她已经申请了
She's already applied!
听着 我没有说这是个骗局
Look, I'm not saying it's a hoax.
有时我们要做的事 是信任
Sometimes, what we do requires a leap of faith.
是相信没人会那样做
To believe when nobody else will.
所以 你真的相信他们吗
So you really do believe them?
是的 我们相信
Yes. We do.
但是没有证据 教堂什么也做不了
But the Church can't do anything without proof.
这才是我们需要的
That's what we need.
好的 我会打电话
Right, listen. I'll make some telephone calls,
看能不能弄到录像设备
see if I can get hold of some video recording equipment.
同时 我和埃德
In the meantime, Ed and I
会跟佩吉和孩子们待在一起
can be spending time with Peggy and the kids,
因为他们需要重回家庭的温暖
because they need to be a family again.
嗨 妈妈 我们回来了
Hi, Mom! We're back!
你们在后面干嘛
What are you doing back?
这些都是什么
What's all this, then?
沃伦夫妇给我们带了红酒
Mr. And Mrs. Warren bought us some vinyls.
还给我们带了猫王的唱片
They got us an Elvis record!
噢 蓝色夏威夷
Oh, Blue Hawaii.
希望你不要介意 有点美国风味
Hope you don't mind. A little American culture.
一点都不介意
Not at all!
- 珍妮特 - 比利
- Janet! - Billy.
我好想你
I missed you.
嗨 大家 我想你们
Hey, guys, I missed you.
你们最近有被欺负吗
So, have any of you ever been bothered by a bully?
皮特 在学校
Pete, at school.
他总是欺负比利
He's always picking on Billy.
亲爱的告诉我 他欺负你时你怎么做的
And, dear, tell me, what do you do when that happens?
他们会帮我
They stick up for me.
这就对了 因为这房子里的幽灵
Good, because the spirit in this house
- 就像是欺负你的人 - 是的
- is a lot like that bully. - Yes.
他欺负珍妮特
And he's got it in for Janet.
你们一定要帮助珍妮特
So you guys gotta stick up for her,
就像他们帮助你一样
the same way they stick up for you.
一家人在一起
Family sticks together.
另一方来说 他们就一定会失败
This, on the other hand, is a lost cause.
噢 天哪
Oh, bloody hell.
所有东西都不能使了
We've had all sorts of things stop working
- 没原因的 - 嗯
- for no reason at all. - Mmm.
我们来点音乐 看看能管用不
We're gonna have music in here one way or another.
那是谁的吉他
Whose guitar is that?
那是爸爸的 但他说我们可以用
Oh, it was Dad's, but he said I could have it.
是吗 介意我用吗
Yeah, do you mind?
不介意
No.
我有点生疏 所以 你们要保证 不能笑我哦
I'm a little rusty, so you gotta promise not to laugh.
特别是你
Especially you.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 不要笑
Hey, don't laugh now.
大家一起唱
Everybody now.
谢谢大家
Thank you very much.
真是又小又轻巧
It's so small and light.
你们为什么要这样做
Why do you do this?
像这样帮助人们
Help people like us?
当你小时候
When you were little,
你有没有曾经担心过
did you ever worry that there might be something
你的床下可能会藏着什么东西
hiding under your bed at night?
对吧 那么
Yeah? Well…
我的床下 真的有东西
My bed actually had something under it.
是啊
Yeah.
有东西抓住我的手把我扯到了地上
Something grabbed my hand and yanked me right to the floor.
太黑了我什么都看不见
It was too dark to see under there,
但是我很快的跑了出去
but let me tell you, I ran out of there so fast.
你知道我爸爸做了什么吗
You know what my dad did?
他把我拽回那个房间
He dragged me right back into
告诉我应该面对我的恐惧
the room and told me I had to face my fears.
但是我怕得要死
And I was scared to death.
我一下子想起修女在教义里告诉我的
But then I remembered what this nun had told me in catechism.
上帝会在任何我们需要的地方
"God will be there for all who need."
所以我从床头柜里 拿出了这个十字架
So, I grabbed this crucifix out from my nightstand, right?
然后我说 不管是什么在那里
And I tell whatever's under there
最好快滚蛋 不然上帝就要惩罚他了
that it better leave, or God was gonna kick its butt.
这是我爸教我做的最棒的事
Best thing my dad ever did for me.
他当然会这样做 因为他并不是真的相信你
Of course he only did it because he really didn't believe me.
我花了好多年寻找 会相信我的人
It took me years to finally find someone who did.
你知道找到后我怕做了什么吗
And you know what I did then?
你娶了她
You married her?
所以你都听说过咯
So you've heard this story before?
好吧
All right.
你做得怎么样啦
How you getting on in here?
嘿 我们弄好了
Hey. We're done here.
也修好衣柜门了
Fixed the closet door, too.
如果你想的话 我可以帮你们看看洗衣机
And if you'd like, I could take a look at the washing machine.
不 我不能让你做那个
No, I couldn't ask you to do that.
底下是一片混乱
It's a disaster down there.
得了吧 能有多坏
Come on. How bad can it be?
噢
Oh.
当我没说
Bloody hell.
里面一切还好吗
Everything still quiet in there?
是的 谢谢上帝 还好
Yes. Thank goodness. Yes.
那一定会是了不起的成就 不是吗
It would be something though, wouldn't it?
如果我们可以证明这个问题
If we were able to prove beyond a shadow of a doubt
那里有东西超生命之上
that there is a life beyond this?
这会是历史性的
It would be historic.
这就是你留下的原因吗
Is that why you're doing this?
因为你想成为历史的一部分吗
Because you want to be a part of something historic?
这不是实验室 这是一个家
This isn't a laboratory, this is someone's house.
而且我认为 帮助这个家庭才是最重要的
And I think helping that family is the only thing that matters.
对不起 我不是那个意思
No, I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
很多年前 我的女儿在车祸中去世了
My daughter died in a car crash several years ago.
在那之后 我开始经历一些事
Afterwards, I started to experience things.
我觉得她想和我联系
I think she wanted to communicate with me.
而且是的 这可以帮助我 如果我能
And, yes, it would help if I knew that she was…
不知道怎么说
I don't know.
能有天堂
Somewhere.
不是那个
That's not it.
噢 看到了
Oh, great.
我觉得我找到了
Think I found it.
好吧
All right.
就在这里
It's right here.
过来拿啊 玛格利特
Come and get it. Margaret!
约翰尼 过来拿啊
Johnny, come and get it.
好吧
Okay.
我能做到
Think I got it.
好了
All right.
就这样
There we go.
那是什么
What's that?
埃德 你 你背后有东西
Ed? There's… There's something behind you.
快过来
What is it?
哦天呢
Oh, Jesus!
哇
Whoa!
佩吉
Peggy!
它抓住我了
He grabbed me.
是他 他想把我拉下去
It was him. He tried to pull me under.
我的天 看
Oh, my God! Look!
噢 天哪 你被抓伤了
Oh God, you're scratched.
这不是抓伤 这是个咬痕
That's not a scratch, that's a bite mark.
就像咬珍妮特那样咬了我
He bit me. Just like he did Janet.
嗷
Aw.
嘿 珍妮特 那个可以给我吗
Hey, Janet, can you get me another one?
好的
Yeah.
珍妮特
Janet?
怎么了
What's wrong?
你看见了吗
Don't you see it?
看见什么
See what?
厨房里
In the kitchen.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you see.
它在玩刀
It's playing with the knives,
藏在暗处
hiding in the dark.
约翰尼 约翰尼 你在干什么
Johnny! Johnny, what you doing?
约翰尼 不 约翰尼 别过去
Johnny, no! Johnny, don't go!
记得沃伦先生说的吗
Remember what Mr. Warren said?
不能被它欺负
We can't let it bully us.
这是我们的房子
This is our house.
约翰尼 约翰尼 求你了快回来
Johnny. Johnny, please come back.
怎么了 发生了什么
What's the matter? What's happened?
珍妮特不见了 她刚刚还和我们站一起
Janet's gone! She was just right here!
快走
Come on.
不
No!
- 妈妈 - 约翰尼
- Mum! - Johnny!
艾德 发生什了么
Ed? What's going on?
妈妈
Mum.
妈妈 约翰尼在里面
Mum, Johnny's in there!
不
No!
约翰尼
Johnny!
退后
Step back.
快啊
Come on.
他们在哪儿 他们在哪儿 约翰尼
Where are they? Where are they? Johnny?
约翰尼
Johnny?
亲爱的
Darling!
哦 亲爱的 来这儿
Oh, darling, come here.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
没事了 亲爱的
It's all right, darling.
没事了
It's all right.
珍妮特呢
Where's Janet?
珍妮特去哪儿了
珍妮特
Janet!
各位 这儿有反应
Guys, I'm picking up something in here.
哦 艾德 小心
Ed, watch the…
我 不会
Me… Won't…
我
Me…
珍妮特
Janet.
没事了 没事了 过来 过来吧
It's okay. It's okay. Come on. Come on.
出来吧
Come on, now.
没事了 当心 小心点
It's okay. Watch out. Look out.
- 慢点 - 好了
- Slowly! - Okay.
亲爱的 没事了
Darling, it's all right.
没事了 妈妈就在这 亲爱的
It's all right, Mum's here. Mum's here, darling.
她怎么进到里面的
How did she get in there?
没事了 亲爱的
It's all right, darling. What's that?
没事了
It's fine.
借过一下
Can I, uh…
这是什么
What is it?
她是装的
She's faking it.
什么
What?
我拿到证据了
I have proof.
对你们的信任重重一击
So much for your leap of faith.
什么
What?
我的女儿才不是假装的 我都看到鬼了
My girl didn't make this up. I've seen things.
她伪装现场的样子都被录下来了
She was caught red-handed faking an event.
不 这不可能 你们有看见那里发生的事情吗
No, it's not possible. Have you seen it in there?
一个12岁的女孩怎么可能把桌子扔过房间
How could a 12-year-old girl throw a table across the room?
都结束了 你还不明白么
It's over. Do you understand?
为了你女儿好
For the sake of your daughter,
别再让这事情变得更难堪了
don't make this harder than it already is.
她自己一个人不可能完成这些事情
She couldn't have pulled this off alone.
哦你怎么敢这么说
Oh, how dare you.
你是认为我让她这么做的
What, you think I put her up to this?
那警察又怎么说呢 他们也是帮凶吗
What about the police? Are they in on this, too?
没事
No, it's all right.
你们呢
What about you two?
你们是相信我们的 对吧
You believe us, don't you?
我们是想帮忙的
We wanna help.
但如果基督教教会看到了录像
But the Church will take one
这件事就会这么结束
look at that video and that'll be the end of it.
他们会想和这类事情撇清关系
They'll wanna distance themselves
这类类似骗局的事情
from anything that remotely resembles a hoax.
请离开 谢谢
I'd like you to leave, please.
请你们出去
Now, go on, get out.
都出去
Get out, the lot of you!
出去
Get out!
也许你可以试着接触那个灵魂
Perhaps, you could somehow reach out to the spirit.
和他进行对话
You know, make contact with it yourself.
我不行 相信我 我试过了
I can't. Believe me, I've tried.
抱歉 我感知不到这里有什么怨灵
I'm sorry, I'm just not sensing anything here.
那就这么结束了
So, that's it, then?
向她们抛出了救生索 又放手了
You hold out a lifeline to them and then you just throw it away?
我们也不想这样
We don't like this any more than you do.
我们会告诉基督教教会所看见的一切
We'll tell the Church about everything we've seen.
但我们所有 唯一确凿的证据
But, the only piece of concrete evidence we've got,
是珍妮特伪造假的事件的录像
is a video of Janet faking an incident.
可是有那么多真的事件发生了
Yeah, but there have been literally dozens of genuine incidents.
你可能用得着这个
You might want this.
就因为她伪装了一次
And, just because she faked it this once,
并不能证明变其他事件也
doesn't change the fact that…
不 这证明了所有的事情
No, it changes everything.
我们是基督教教会的代理人
We're agents of the Church here.
就算佩吉没赶我们走 教会也会让我们回去
They'd be calling us home even if Peggy hadn't asked us to leave.
你在这儿给了很多支持 莫里斯
You've done really good work here, Maurice.
在没有人帮助她们的时候 你一直在
You were here for them when no one else was.
谢谢
Uh, thank you.
但有时 你需要对信仰抱有信心
But, sometimes you need to make a leap of faith.
当没有人相信的时候 坚守自己的信念
Believe when nobody else will.
感觉不对劲
This doesn't feel right.
我懂
I know.
一路平安
Have a safe trip.
真的是你在假装吗
Did you really do it?
弄坏厨房 还有那些所有的
Wreck the kitchen and all that?
为什么啊
But, why?
它说要杀了你们
It said it would kill you,
如果我没把他们赶走
if I didn't make them leave.
你不觉得这有点巧吗
Don't you think it's a little convenient
她正好就选了
that she just happened to fake an incident
那间屋子的那个房间里伪造事件
in the one room of the
而且刚好对着摄像头
house that had a video camera pointing at it?
是的
Yeah.
不好
No.
糟了
Oh, damn it.
罗琳
Lorraine.
帮我整理下这些录像带
Help me set up these tape recorders.
从孔里穿过去 从头开始放
Thread it through and start it from the top.
好的
All right.
还记得珍妮特那些混乱的信息吗
Remember those strange, garbled messages we got from Janet?
- 就是比尔的那些 - 记得
- You know, from Bill? - Yes.
一共有两条 对吧
There were two of them, right?
这是第一条
Here's the first one.
救命
Help! It…
快放开
Let go!
救我 放 手
Help! It… Let…
字幕
Go!
我们之前认为这是说他自己 对吧
We thought he was referring to himself, right?
- 是的 - 听第二条
- Yes. - Listen to the second one.
我 不会
Me… Won't…
我
Me…
如果我推理得没错的话
If I'm right about this…
救我 它不会让我走的
Help me! It won't let me go!
我来这儿是为了见我家人
I come here to see my family.
但他们现在不在这儿了
But they're not here now.
我觉得
I think,
我现在可以走了
I'd like to go now.
- 但我不能走 - 为什么
- But I can't. - Why not?
它想要她 非常想要
It wants her. So badly.
它几乎要得到她了
It almost has her.
告诉我怎么阻止他
Tell me how to stop it.
我在给予 也在略夺
I'm given and I'm taken.
你一出生的时候我就存在了
I was there at your first breath.
你没有开口
You didn't ask for me.
但我会一直跟随你直到死去
But I'll follow you till death.
等等 我不明白
Wait. I don't understand.
求你了
Please…
天啊
Oh, God!
你流血了
You're bleeding!
发生了什么
What is happening?
那个老人的灵魂只是个傀儡
The old man's spirit is just a pawn.
他已经被奴役了来磨损珍妮特的意志
He's been enslaved to where he's to weaken Janet's will.
被奴役了 被谁奴役
Enslaved? Enslaved by who?
被某种没有人性的东西
Something inhuman.
它以一种残忍的方式来攻击我的信念
Something that's taken a blasphemous form to attack my faith.
那间屋子里有鬼
There is a demonic presence in that house.
你要在维克离开之前找到他 我们得回去
You need to get Vic before he leaves. We need to go back.
好
Okay.
妈妈救我 求你了
Mom, help me, please! Mom!
救我 妈妈 求你了
Please, Mom, help me! Help!
上帝啊 离我们远点
For God's sake, leave us alone!
玛格利特
Margaret!
玛格利特 不要
Margaret, no!
快 我们快从这出去
Come on, let's get out of here!
快 我们快出去
Come on, let's get out!
- 快去佩吉家 - 你不去吗
- Go to Peggy's house! - What, you're not coming?
我去找珍妮特
I can't leave Janet!
- 不 珍妮特 - 妈妈
- No! Janet! - Mum!
珍妮特
Janet!
我没听明白
Well, I don't understand it.
一开始你说那不是真的 现在又说是真的
I mean, first you say it's not real, now it is.
她的视线被鬼蒙蔽了
Her sight was being blocked by the inhuman spirit.
那个老人的灵魂
The old man's spirit
无法穿破 直到我们离开那间屋子
couldn't break through until we left that house.
他们所经历的一切
Everything they've experienced
都证明了鬼的存在
has been a manifestation of the demonic.
老人 驼背的人 都只是蒙蔽我们的表象
The Old Man, the Crooked Man, they're just a facade,
好让我们看不到那间屋子里真正的鬼
trying to keep us from seeing the real evil in that house.
在我看来 他想帮我 但他太害怕了
In my vision, he wanted to help me, but he was too afraid.
所以他嘴里不停地说暗号
And he kept speaking in a kind of riddle.
他一直说 我在给予 我也在掠夺
Something like, uh, "I am given and I am taken.
我从你刚出现时就在那儿了
"I was there at your first breath.
你没有开口要
"You didn't ask for me.
但会一直跟随你 直到你死去
"But I will follow you until your death."
是名字 不是你要来的
Your name. You didn't ask for it.
但你刚出生时就给你了
It was given, when you were born.
就是这样 知道了恶魔的名字
That's it! Knowing the demon's
我们就有了战胜它的力量
name gives us power over it and we can cast it out.
是的 没错 但我们不知道它的名字
Yeah, sure, but we don't know its name.
我们有可能知道
But, maybe we do.
呃
Huh?
要不然他为什么给我们这个线索呢
Why else would he give us that clue?
他肯定觉得我们知道名字
He must think that we know it somehow.
所以你们现在怎么办
So, what do you do now?
面对一个强大到足以蒙蔽罗琳的鬼魂
An inhuman spirit powerful enough to cloud Lorraine's sight
这超乎了我的承受范围
is more than a match for me.
我们要在它杀了珍妮特之前 把她带去教堂
We need to get Janet to the Church before it kills her.
珍妮特
Janet!
发生了什么
What happened?
珍妮特
Janet!
噢谢天谢地你在这儿
Thank God you're here.
- 珍妮特在里面 - 快啊
- Janet's in there! - Come on!
该死的
Damn it.
啊
Huh?
- 艾德 你还好么 - 嗯
- Ed! Are you okay? - Yeah!
我去后面看一下
I'm gonna go around back!
不 艾德 别去
No! Ed! No!
艾德 别去
Ed, no, no, no.
我和你一起去
I'm gonna come with you!
- 佩吉 待着别动 - 珍妮特
- Peggy, stay here. - Janet!
- 在车里和孩子们一起等着 别动 - 珍妮特
- Wait in the car with the kids! Wait! - Janet!
珍妮特
Janet!
上车
Get in the car.
快 快去 你也是 佩吉 快来
Go in, go on. You, too, Peggy. Come on!
艾德
Ed?
别这样
No! Come on!
艾德
Ed!
它开不了的
It won't open!
我试试
Let me try.
- 我们得把它砸了 - 好吧
- We need to break it down! - All right.
- 在这等着 - 把它砸了
- Wait here. - Break it!
艾德 就在那里等着
Ed, hon, wait right there.
等一下 维克马上就回来
Wait. Vic'll be right back.
我等不了 我去找她
I can't wait. I'm going on ahead.
不 艾德 不 停下
No, Ed, don't! Stop!
你不能一个人去对付这些
You can't fight this alone.
她需要我们的帮助
She needs our help!
艾德 拜托了 拜托就在那里等我们
Ed, please. Please, just wait for me.
请等等我
Please wait for me.
我不能失去你 我很害怕
I can't lose you. I am so scared.
我知道
I know.
我也是
Me, too.
但我必须去帮她
But I have to help her.
万一预景成真了呢
But, what about my vision?
我知道 我对你许过诺言 亲爱的
I know I made a promise to you, hon,
但我必须去
but I have to do this.
我爱你 罗琳
I love you, Lorraine.
艾德 不 不
Ed, no! No!
停下 别去
Stop! Don't!
艾德
Ed!
不
No!
不 停下
No. Stop.
艾德 有人吗 救命
Ed! Someone! Help!
让开
Move.
噢天呢
Oh, God.
珍妮特 你在哪
Janet, where are you?
快啊
Come on!
救命
Help!
珍妮特
Janet!
救救我
Help me!
珍妮特
Janet!
以父、子、圣灵之名
In the name of the Father, and the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
你的
What's your…
你的名字
What's your name?
我知道你的名字
I do know your name.
我问过你
I asked you.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are!
你告诉过我
And you told me.
你告诉过我你的名字
You told me your name.
我记下来了
And I wrote it down.
我需要我的圣经
I need my Bible!
为什么 发生了什么
Why? What's happening?
什么
What…
恶魔的名字 赐予我们力量吧
The demon's name gives us power over it.
V
V.
A L
A. L.
A K
A. K.
瓦拉克
Valak.
珍妮特
Janet!
Janet?
从前有个歪歪扭扭的疯子
There was a crooked man
走了一英里歪歪扭扭的路
And he walked a crooked mile
手拿歪歪扭扭的六便士 踏上歪歪扭扭的台阶
He found a crooked sixpence upon a crooked stile
买了一只歪歪扭扭的猫儿 猫儿抓着歪歪扭扭的老鼠
He bought a crooked cat which caught a crooked mouse
他们一起住歪歪扭扭的小屋
And they all lived together in a little…
维克 维克 让我过去
Vic! Vic! Let me through.
- 不 等等 罗琳 让我试试 - 我要进去了 不
- No, wait, Lorraine, let me try. - I'm going! No!
让我进来 罗琳
Let me go in. Lorraine!
艾德
Ed!
罗琳
Lorraine!
艾德
Ed!
珍妮特
Janet?
珍妮特 不 不
Janet! No! No!
我抓住你啦
I got you.
上来
Come on.
不
No!
珍妮特
Janet.
艾德 艾德
Ed! Ed!
嗷
Ah!
艾德
Ed!
罗琳
Lorraine!
艾德
Ed!
你的名字让我得以控制你 恶魔
Your name gives me dominion over you, demon.
我知道你的名字
And I do know your name!
你是瓦拉克
You are Valak!
亵渎者
The defiler.
不敬的 邪窟里的
The profane, the marquis of snakes!
以父、子、圣灵之名
In the name of the Father and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit,
我诅咒你回到地狱
I condemn you back to hell!
不
No!
艾德
Ed!
上来
Come on!
艾德
Ed!
行了 我们很好 行了
Okay. We're good. Okay.
- 艾德 你还好么 - 去看看她怎么样
- Ed, are you okay? - No, check on her.
珍妮特
Janet?
天哪 她还好吗
Oh, my God! Is she all right?
我去叫救护车
I'll call an ambulance.
珍妮特 坐起来 亲爱的 坐起来
Janet, sit up, darling. Sit up.
就是这样
Here you go now.
深呼吸
Take a big, deep breath.
字幕
Big, deep breath. There you go.
你还好么
You all right?
他会好起来的
He'll be fine.
- 她还好吗 - 是的 她很好
- Does she look all right? - Yeah, she's fine.
你救了她
You saved her.
不
No.
你救了我们
You saved us.
我有告诉过你 这是命中注定的么
Didn't I tell you it was meant to be?
但你相信了我
But you believed in me.
没有你 我不可能做到的
I couldn't have done it without you.
谢谢你们为了我们回来
Thanks for coming back for us.
噢
Oh.
嗷
Aw.
来 坐这儿 坐下
Here, sit down. Sit down.
你知道
You know…
自我儿童时期起 它一直保护着我
This has kept me safe since I was a kid.
我希望你戴着它
I want you to have it.
当你长大后
And, when you grow up, you
发现有人需要它 就转赠给他们吧
find someone who needs it, you give it to them.
如何
Deal?
我真的很幸运
I'm so lucky.
你说过 一个人就可以改变一切
You said one person could change everything.
但是
But…
我拥有这样的两个人
I've got two.
之后 恩菲尔德闹鬼事件成为了 超自然历史记录上有名的案子之一
佩吉·霍奇斯继续在格林街的这栋房子里度过她的余生
2003年 她坐在客厅的一把椅子上安详的离开
正是40年前比尔·威尔金斯去世时那把椅子
噢
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
告诉我开始的事 第一个晚上发生了什么
Tell me about the beginning, the first night of your happening.
你弟弟在干嘛
What was your brother doing?
他在玩耍闲荡
Brothers playing and fooling about.
我不确定
I wasn't quite sure, no.
- 他们都很害怕 - 是的 他们目瞪口呆
- They were scared? - Yeah, petrified.
珍妮特呢 她怎样
Janet? What about Janet?
它从你那出来时
When it comes from your area,
珍妮特 你有没有感觉喉咙里有东西
Janet, do you feel anything in your throat?
- 没有 - 你什么感觉都没有吗
- No. - You just don't feel anything?
现在 我看着珍妮特
Now, I'm looking at Janet.
不要在这打架
Don't fight in here.
她发出了声音
And the voice comes from her,
但是她嘴巴没动 哪里都没动
but her mouth doesn't move and nothing moves.
关了它
Turn it off!
我知道
I know…
珍妮特 能不能在声音出现时告诉我
Janet, can you tell when the voice is gonna come through you?
不 不 我不会
No. No, I don't ever.
你知道我是谁吗 你知道我的名字吗
You know who I am? Do you know what my name is?
是的 艾德 艾德
Yeah. Ed. Ed!
你是基督徒么
Were you a Christian?
不 这你是知道的
No! You know it!
你什么时候死的 你还记得么
What year did you die? Do you remember?
是的 我已经死了 61岁的时候
Yeah. I'm dead. Sixty-one.
1961年
Nineteen sixty-one.